Developers

Network

Ecosystem

en

🇺🇸

en

🇺🇸

© Livepeer, Inc. 2024

Privacy Policy
--------------

Last Updated: April 15, 2021
----------------------------

Livepeer, Inc. (**"Livepeer"**, **"we"** or **"us"**) is committed to protecting your privacy. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to describe to you our practices regarding the Personal Data (as defined below) we collect from users of this user registration website (the **"Site"**). The purpose (the **"Purpose"**) of this Site is to allow you to register to receive Livepeer tokens (**"LPT"**) solely for use on the Livepeer network (the **"Network"**) as a staking token (which is explained in more detail in our participation agreement at livepeer.org/participation-agreement (the **"Participation Agreement"**) and for us to distribute the Livepeer tokens in accordance with the Participation Agreement. Any term that is capitalized and is not defined in this Privacy Policy has the meaning provided in the Participation Agreement.

**1\. User Consent.** By submitting Personal Data through our Site or Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Without limiting the foregoing, you agree to the processing of your Personal Data in connection with the Purpose, including compliance with any regulatory requirements.

**2\. Types of Data We Collect.** **"Personal Data"** means data that allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, as well as any other non-public information about you that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing data.**"Anonymous Data"** means data that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Data; Anonymous Data does not, by itself, permit the identification of individual persons. We collect Personal Data and Anonymous Data, as described below.

**3\. Information You Provide to Us.**

**4.** We may collect Personal Data from you, such as your first and last name, phone number, e-mail address, country of residence, and mailing addresses and password when you register on the Site (**"Registration"**).

**5.** In connection with regulatory requirements, we or our third party providers may collect your social security number, date of birth, address history and photo images of you. In the alternative, we or our third party provider may use the phone number that you have provided to collect the social security number, date of birth and address history associated with such phone number(s) from other parties to allow us to comply with the regulatory requirements.

**6.** We may associate your phone number to your mobile device identification information.

**7.** If you provide us feedback or contact us via e-mail, we will collect your name and e-mail address, as well as any other content included in the e-mail, in order to send you a reply.

**8.** We also collect other types of Personal Data that you provide to us voluntarily, such as your operating system and version and other requested information if you contact us via e-mail regarding support for the Services.

**9.** We may also collect Personal Data at other points in our Site that state that Personal Data is being collected.

**10\. Cookies.**

**11**. Like many websites, we use Cookies to collect information. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing the website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Services. This type of information is collected to make the Site more useful to you and to tailor the experience with us to meet your special interests and needs. We use two broad categories of Cookies: (1) first party Cookies, served directly by us to your computer or mobile device, which are used only by us to recognize your computer or mobile device when it uses the Services; and (2) third party Cookies, which are served by service providers on our Services, and can be used by such service providers to recognize your computer or mobile device when it visits other websites.

**12.** Our Services use the following types of Cookies for the purposes set out below:

| Type of Cookies | Purpose |
| --- | --- |
| Essential Cookies | These Cookies are essential to provide you with services available through our Services and to enable you to use some of its features. For example, they allow you to log in to secure areas of our Services and help the content of the pages you request load quickly. Without these Cookies, the services that you have asked for cannot be provided, and we only use these Cookies to provide you with those services. |
| Functionality Cookies | These Cookies allow our Services to remember choices you make when you use our Services, remembering your login details and remembering the changes you make to other parts of our Site/Application(s)/Service which you can customize. The purpose of these Cookies is to provide you with a more personal experience and to avoid you having to re-enter your preferences every time you visit our Services. |
| Analytics and Performance Cookies | These Cookies are used to collect information about traffic to our Services and how users use our Services. The information gathered does not identify any individual visitor. The information is aggregated and anonymous. It includes the number of visitors to our Services, the websites that referred them to our Services, the pages they visited on our Services, what time of day they visited our Services, whether they have visited our Services before, and other similar information. We use this information to help operate our Services more efficiently, to gather broad demographic information and to monitor the level of activity on our Site/Application(s)/Services. We use Google Analytics and other third party analytics services for this purpose. Google Analytics uses its own Cookies. It is only used to improve how our Services works. You can find out more information about Google Analytics Cookies here: [https://developers.google.com/analytics/resources/concepts/gaConceptsCookies](https://developers.google.com/analytics/resources/concepts/gaConceptsCookies). You can find out more about how Google protects your data here: www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html. You can prevent the use of Google Analytics relating to your use of our Services by downloading and installing the browser plugin available via this link: [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB). |

**13\. Information Collected via Technology**

**14\. Information Collected by Our Servers.** To make our Site more useful to you, our servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) collect information from you, including your browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol ("IP") address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet, which may vary from session to session), domain name, and/or a date/time stamp for your visit.

**15\. Log Files.** As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes IP addresses, browser type, Internet service provider ("ISP"), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users' movements around the Site, gather demographic information about our user base as a whole, and better tailor our Services to our users' needs.

**16\. Pixel Tags.** In addition, we may use "Pixel Tags" (also referred to as clear Gifs, Web beacons, or Web bugs). Pixel Tags are tiny graphic images with a unique identifier, similar in function to Cookies, that are used to track online movements of Web users. In contrast to Cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, Pixel Tags are embedded invisibly in Web pages. Pixel Tags also allow us to send e-mail messages in a format users can read, and they tell us whether e-mails have been opened to ensure that we are sending only messages that are of interest to our users. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to a user. We do not tie the information gathered by Pixel Tags to our users' Personal Data.

**17\. How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals.** We do not currently respond to "do not track" signals or other mechanisms that might enable Users to opt out of tracking on our site.

(a) **Information Collected from You About Others.** **Information Collected from Third Party Companies.** We may receive Personal and/or Anonymous Data about you from companies that provide services to us in connection with the Purpose. We may add this information to the information we have already collected from you via our Site for use in connection with the Purpose, including to ensure compliance with regulatory compliance.

**18\. Use of Your Personal Data**

**19\. General Use.** In general, Personal Data you submit to us is used in connection with the Purpose, including compliance with regulatory requirements or to respond to your queries. We use your Personal Data in the following ways:

* facilitate your Registration;
* identify you as a user in our system;
* provide improved administration of our Site and

**20\. Creation of Anonymous Data.** We may create Anonymous Data records from Personal Data by excluding information (such as your name) that makes the data personally identifiable to you. We use this Anonymous Data to analyze request and usage patterns so that we may enhance the content of our Services and improve Site navigation. We reserve the right to use Anonymous Data and aggregated and other de-identified information for any purpose and disclose Anonymous Data to third parties in our sole discretion.

**21\. Disclosure of Your Personal Data.** We disclose your Personal Data as described below and as described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy.

**22\. Third Party Service Providers.** We may share your Personal Data with third party service providers to: provide you with the Services that we offer you through our Site; to conduct quality assurance testing; to facilitate creation of accounts; to provide technical support; and/or to provide other services to the Company.

**23\. Corporate Restructuring.** We may share some or all of your Personal Data in connection with or during negotiation of any merger, financing, acquisition or dissolution transaction or proceeding involving sale, transfer, divestiture, or disclosure of all or a portion of our business or assets. In the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, Personal Data may also be transferred as a business asset. If another company acquires our company, business, or assets, that company will possess the Personal Data collected by us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy.

**24\. Other Disclosures.** Regardless of any choices you make regarding your Personal Data (as described below), Company may disclose Personal Data if it believes in good faith that such disclosure is necessary (i) in connection with any legal investigation; (ii) to comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on Company; (iii) to protect or defend the rights or property of Company or users of the Site or Services; and/or (iv) to investigate or assist in preventing any violation or potential violation of the law, this Privacy Policy, or the Participation Agreement.

**25\. Third Party Websites.** Our Site may contain links to third party websites. When you click on a link to any other website or location, you will leave our Site and go to another site, and another entity may collect Personal Data or Anonymous Data from you. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for, these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites or content, or to any collection of your Personal Data after you click on links to such outside websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of every website you visit. The links to third party websites or locations are for your convenience and do not signify our endorsement of such third parties or their products, content or websites.

Third-party web sites include:

**26\. Your Choices Regarding Information.** You have several choices regarding the use of information on our Service:

**27\. Email Communications.** We will periodically send you e-mails that directly promote the LPT or the Site. When you receive promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us and you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail you receive or by contacting us directly (please see contact information below). Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you service related communications, including notices of any updates to the Participation Agreement or Privacy Policy.

**28\. Cookies.** If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to accept Cookies for any of the purposes described above, then you can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting Cookies or to prompt you before accepting a Cookie from the websites you visit. Consult your browser's technical information. If you do not accept Cookies, however, you may not be able to use all functionality of the Site. If you have any questions about how to disable or modify Cookies, please let us know at the contact information provided below.

**29\. Changing or Deleting Your Personal Data.** All users may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Data in their user account by contacting us at the address listed below. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honor your request. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. If you request a modification of any Personal Data, we may not be able to provide you with LPT.

**30\. Transfer of Personal Information Outside the EEA.** Your information, including Personal Information that we collect from you, may be transferred to, stored at and processed by us and our affiliates and other third parties outside the country in which you reside, including, but not limited to the United States, where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world. By using the Site, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this policy.

**31\. Automated Decision-Marking.** We do not use your Personal Information for the purposes of automated decision-making. However, we may do so in order to fulfil obligations imposed by law, in which case we will inform you of any such processing and provide you with an opportunity to object.

**32\. Data Retention Periods.** We will only retain your Personal Information as long as reasonably required in connection with the Purpose or as otherwise required or permitted in connection with applicable law (for example, for regulatory purposes).

**33\. Changes to This Privacy Policy.** This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy at siafunds.tech/privacy and we will change the "Last Updated" date above. You should consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

**34\. Questions; Contacting Company; Reporting Violations.** If you have any questions or concerns or complaints about our Privacy Policy or our data collection or processing practices, or if you want to report any security violations to us, please contact us at the following address or phone number:

Livepeer, Inc.  
85 Broad Street  
New York, NY 10004  
Attn: Privacy

Ecosystem

Developers

Resources

Community

About Livepeer.org

Copyright © 2024 Livepeer, Inc.
